Finding Aid for the Getty Research Institute Scholars Program Images and Recordings, 1985-2013 IA20026
Institutional Records and Archives
- Photographs, 1985-2007; Series III.; 31.85 Linear Feet (33 boxes)
  - Scholar portraits: contact sheets, negatives, and photograhic prints, 1985-2007; 30.75 Linear Feet (31 boxes)
    - 2004-2005:
      - Postdoctoral Fellows
        - Sarah Adams (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 11)
        - Elizabeth Kotz (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 12)
        - Carrie Lambert-Beatty (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 13)
      - Scholar portraits on DVD
        - GRI Scholar 2005, DVD1, (DVD) (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 14)
        - GRI Scholar 2005, DVD2, (DVD) (Box 2006.IA.24-9, Folder 15)
    - 2007:
      - Orlan, 1 Linear Feet (1 oversize photograph) (Box 2009.IA.41-01, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified scholars, 1985-2005
      Undated photographs of unidentified scholars from within the date range of collected materials, 1985-2005.
      - Portrait of unidentified scholar, undated; (includes 1 oversize photograph) (Box 2006.IA.24-1, Folder 2)
      - Damaged oversize prints of various scholars, 1985-1996 (Box 2006.IA.24-1, Folder 3)
        Includes photograps of Ginzburg, Riese, Schwartz, Schlitt, Lowry, and O'Connell. One photograph is unlabeled and undated.
      - Portrait of unidentified scholar, undated; (Framed oversize photograph) (Box 2006.IA.24-12)